sound to me free lip
you won't sink my battleship my beard is
older than you are there better be no
Penguins on this space Here's your old
cheese back come stay out of my way
no one messes with the beard thought I'd
forget
not bad but I think I could do better
huh I need some Elves for this
Santa torbjorn is here
I'm jolly old Saint torbjorn
Ahoy matey
shiver me timbers
run a shot across the bow they've
blocked the payload
stop twiddling your thumbs and move the
payload get this hunk of junk moving
layer popping back like daisies those
suckers keep coming back they keep
coming I'll keep building enemies coming
back what is this witchcraft eliminate
this target some assembly required
they walk straight into that who's
counting I am
a beautiful shot
efficient hurry up and revive me I'm not
doing so well I need to be revived let's
get started
now it's going to get interesting hence
cold and ready to go
just look at you
show them what you've got hi far see
great things for you you're all set up
my dear make sure maker proud ah such
potential they're going to love this
turret in position
I have big plans for you show them what
you can do hive high hopes for you a
thing of beauty
turret deployed protect our flag defend
the flag we still need someone to stay
near the terminal come on let's get over
to the payload keeping my eye on this
position I'll keep watch here watching
this area over here I'm right here
there's more where that came from
I'll get you running like new again just
a little touch up a little mending's all
you need let's patch you up don't you
break on me yet don't worry I'll patch
you up
I'll fix you up oh you have your good as
new hold it together fix and you write
up it's just a scratch defend with me
I'm defending
follow me and defend get out of there
there's an enforcer keep some distance
from that enforcer help
I could use some help here I need help
don't let up now we've almost destroyed
it the payloads moving as fast as it can
Gabriel I need someone to babysit the
payload no one ever stays near the
payload it'll make it I hope where's the
fun in that the payload's taking
significant damage they need to keep the
omnics from getting through enemy
Bastion in front enemy Bastion on the
right enemy Bastion on the left
enemy Bastion up ahead enemy Bastion
behind us defend the objective we wiped
them out that's a job well done got them
all
oops my mistake sorry
Oopsy Daisy ah rookies don't let it get
to you rookie they have a job to do
why am I not surprised it was only a
matter of time before this happened
again and strap a lot of bots that's
enough from you Dr junkenstein a Reaper
is dead
for now
you're magic does not impress me
you call that a monster the witch is
slain what can I say Best of the Best
really I take a look at that damn tour
it ahead not one of mine enemy turret
ahead enemy turret ahead peace or strap
attack the objective keep moving this
way just start hammering My ultimate is
almost ready they took the robot dog
lick them take the robot they have to
get the robot back
um
assassins on you she's on you that's all
they fuss about easy as pie they're
drooping up here
no
hey
have two chances to get the job done
let's do it in one no hiccups so far
let's keep it that way
one more win nothing to it Vikings are
the greatest Raiders of wealth and
treasure the world has ever seen it's
good to fight alongside someone I know I
can trust where I'm from we throw
deserters into the sea do you have
somewhere to be I do not trust him in
his strange Gods
Not For the last time I hope
instead of hunting Dragons I'm stuck
here fighting these mechanical
monstrosities made by a Madman not
another word rookie let's keep it that
way seems like we hit another little
snag maybe I should just blow us all up
right now forget about it defend the
payload it just needs a little more time
it's going to work trust me I'm giving
it all I've got you're making a chicken
out of a Feather getting rid of the flag
dropping the flag
consider it charity that's not the way
it was supposed to go that's an
interesting one got one I picked up a
little something special got it package
secured secured time for a rework a
little modification I have a better idea
time to upgrade needs iteration
let's give you some adjusting
incoming keep them off the payload I
can't do any repairs to it here it's got
to stay in one piece until we get to the
door I feel great much better
ah back to work yes it's not a costume
still missing a few crafts people here
we're still reassembling this workshop's
feeling a little empty
I'm going in the reaper has joined the
battle the witch is here the Summoner
has returned hop there Dr junkenstein
monster is Among Us I'm unstoppable
watch out I'm boiling hot
upgraded
converts to Ragnarok
boost it up
we are not going to lose get your head
screwed on street they can still finish
someone needs to get on the terminal
they're wasting time here it's coming
over the ramparts what's the left shark
Tire on the left
stop the robot come on stop their push
protect the door they must clear the
door they have reached the door over
here
returning the favor doctor I'll get you
fixed up in no time you're not leaving
me not yet you can take more than that
get back in the fight come on you rust
nut show them What You're Made Of up and
at them they still need you Angela back
to battle with you hop an atom made to
order
sniper vertical she's gone come on team
they have to stop that sniper finish him
off have his wounded Bingo now we're
getting somewhere come on baby
just wait and see what I have in mind
come on how about this
oh damn machine
that'll do
completion date
then it's done the payload's really
falling apart it can't take too many
more hits like this how did they get so
far they're catching up to us they have
to stop them before they overtake us
shark Tire on the right it's coming from
the right vote our right flank they
outnumber us careful we're outnumbered
so we'll knock him down she can't take
anymore she's going to blow pick on
someone your own size my babies
destroyed my precious work
my turret I've hurt hard on that my baby
too hot for you need healing I need
healing let's do this I can't help but
think they're going about this the wrong
way then are we going to learn you just
can't trust an omnic what does this null
sector want anyways
foreign
I'm getting better all the time
I'm expanding my horizons wonder who
designed that little gym
a Marvel of engineering don't you think
pretty useful if I do say so myself
I designed that you know calibration
spot on
oops did I leave that there
I see you fell from my new anti-rine
heart turret technology you can't Mass
produce that takes after her maker
that's what I made you for sorry Lena it
was the turret not me my little
assistant
a Marvel of craftsmanship don't you
think do you appreciate my craftsmanship
now that's a turret function and Beauty
torbjorn ready to work
you don't know what they're capable of
look around you this has happened before
and it'll happen again damn tin cans you
just can't trust them tell them to be
careful with it it's fragile tell them
to watch The Landing here it comes let's
hope those guns really are down back to
work
[Music]
I'll just take a little break
don't mind me
leave this to an expert taking the lead
ha leaving them in the dust
forging ahead
setting out the welcome mat generators
are green propulsion systems are waking
up I needed a longer moment I need a
moment there's nothing I can do just be
patient he just needs a moment to get
warmed up damn machines are not worried
about casualties just a little bit
longer they'll have to force our way
through
smash through that obstacle
breakthrough so we can proceed points
secured at the point now get over here I
got the objective huh this is a good
place to set up let's set up here this
is it let's not screw it up let's get
the job done we are almost there
catching up the lead is almost ours I
Smell Trouble Brewing take cover
exhibit a gravity
enjoy the Free Fall hope you packed your
wings
enjoy your flight off you go
keep them off the robot and we'll win
hurry take the robot got it there we go
time to roll up my sleeves I still have
some fight in me back to the beginning
I've been rebjorn guess you can learn
even at this age let's get to work well
I'm just getting warmed up back down not
a chance a good pop always gets it
working again though I'm starting to
regret having designed all their weapons
her lint home never gives up back at it
running back to base I have the flag
don't mention it you're welcome get off
your butt and stop the payload go stall
that payload are you on the cinnamon the
payload's moving fake us over block the
payload
hello
hi hello hello hey my warmest greetings
for The Horde it was nice while it
lasted let's not buy the pig while it's
still in the bag let's capture the
objective
trust me through here this way press the
attack for the last time I'm Swedish I'm
standing right here need to find a space
big enough to drop the payload fold back
get ready it's gonna blow
there we go get ready for this
hey
[Applause]
oh
something for me
I'm not one to turn down a reward
oh
what do we have here
working as intended I'm with you I'm at
your side
ah better
ha back to work thanks for the help
we're running out of time focus on those
last units they're running out of time
focus on those or 14s Mercy are you
doing all right keep them off it those
slicers are going to destroy the payload
hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
in three two one
three two one
huh
[Music]
if you build it they will die get ready
it's firing up understood thanks for the
vote of confidence armor come get it
armor up come get your armor armor over
here armor here watch me shake my claw
I'm not the dwarf but I'll give you more
solid down to my molten core
make some turrets
usually they say Make some noise so that
was a joke hurry up come on what are we
waiting for hmm I wonder if there's
something I should be doing the Viking
sort of dragon but a dragon found him
first
come on silence the doctor he's getting
on my nerves Kill The the reaper
still leaves kill that infernal Summoner
we need to kill the monster
Armor's still there
no one wants some armor the armors just
sit in there got an enemy here watch out
for this one Fire's an enemy here there
they are let's show them what's what
oh
Mindy beard huh
holy standing around all this work to be
done Winston are you still use a match
silly feather duster of a con Anna they
all thought you were dead why does
everyone keep pestering me about my
aardvarks
any chance you'd let me peek under the
hood of your Mech
there's something on your dress
believe me I don't need reminding
no one asked for your opinion how in the
world does this place even work your
armor seems to be working well I guess
you were right about the core
integration design whoever built your
Mech did a good job none of that AI mess
I'd love to get a look at that Fusion
core I was wondering if I could take a
look at your little robot ring out wild
Bells just try to keep it in one piece
for once
I don't like this standing around maybe
this year you can be the elf I think
Ingrid's been working on something how's
briquita doing keeping everything in
working order I hate working with these
talking tin cans I hate working with
these talking tin cans I sometimes
wonder if all that armor slows your
brain down
fariha any plans for the winter even the
one about the Mad Doctor and the witch
who asked me the Brits have their hits
on straight Dominic writes duh
Angela you should know that no one could
stop brigitta from doing something she
had her mind set on she's a leaned home
after all
ah this brings me back you know fariha I
could take a look at fixing up your suit
if you'd like this place is like the
terrible culmination of a thousand of my
worst nightmares are you kidding me why
does that feel like an accusation
Reinhardt you'd better not be feeling my
daughter's head with stories isn't it
enough to be an engineer Brigitte and I
think a hammer upside your face would
suit you the quality of the
craftsmanship here hurts my soul last I
checked I didn't ask for your opinion
who need to stop telling those
ridiculous stories Reinhardt No One
Believes they're real not bad no not bad
I'm glad you let me add a little
something to it
now this is my kind of factory
Reinhardt least number of eliminations
buys the post Mission drinks hey stop
following me around shoe
such intriguing Sonic displacement
technology doc the life and having
diversed headaches yeah
Everyone's a Critic I don't want to talk
about it but a terrifying thought
well it just so happened she had some
saved for you I'm ready
I found the shield well I found the
shield generator they need to get
together before we can continue
enemy turret down
shoddy workmanship enemy turret down
clearly not one of mine hold your thumbs
and we'll get through this all right
sure
you drive a hard bargain are you ever
going to tell me valkyrie's airfoil
ratio like take buns but we'll get it
done don't you beat boot me no is no
for the last time tell ganymy my beard
is not a nest brigitta isn't meddling
too much with your armor is she he'll
always be my little girl who developed
those orbs of yours
Baptiste does it how did a mercenary
like yourself come by such Advanced
Technologies why thank you I must admit
I'm surprised hey
let's go I've got a few new inventions
to try
we're still alive and kicking brigata
did you check if you brought enough
repair packs for everyone that was once
Bastion I bet you haven't had assistance
check in years who knows what kind of
weird behaviors you picked up you don't
know do you retirement looks good on you
Anna I wish we could get that
immortality feel to work on my turret
how many have used Scoundrels are
missing a leg remind me to install a
firewall system in you can't be too
careful nowadays
inspire me your fishy information
I prefer my two feet on the ground how
about you let me build you a new Mech
you can't be serious Hammer check turret
check back up to her attack second
through fourth back up turrets check
check and check still a one-man Posse
that's Parenthood for you no I thought I
left OverWatch but here we are
what about a turret that shoots smaller
turrets and what are you willing to bet
no they mostly hang out in that arcology
of theirs Dr Joe you've made quite the
name for yourself
yes and they still won't let me help
well they can't all have Ultra powerful
gauntlets and they are maybe too much
don't you ever want to settle down I'm
looking forward to working with you if
you ever need a punching bag I got
plenty of metal that needs scrapping you
shouldn't believe everything Mercy says
you know quit being so humble nothing
wrong with being proud of your work uh
I guess it takes all kinds to make a
world I bet my turrets are better shot
than you yes well let's get this done
maybe you need better friends oh with
this many Engineers on the team we can
handle any problem that comes our way
let me talk to him face to face don't
roll over me you're here I'm not a
bowling pin this is not the reunion I
expected if you can't cut them nail them
like mother like daughter Cassidy said
he wanted a bigger grenade so I built
him one then he said no this is too
large I need it to fit in my hand well
he should have been more clear the damn
Tower I don't care if tourists like it
it's falling over and it needs to be
fixed the Lind home reputation now I
can't believe I fell for all that
anti-omnic claptrap well I'm known to be
an excellent teacher fine but just a few
blueprints I'm a little embarrassed of
some of the things I said here but I'm
doing my best to learn
I've got some powder for that doctors
always wanting you to do the work now
this is a city that understands
engineering and that child genius
a future Ironclad no doubt hey someone
repaired my turret while I was napping
you know for real it's not a sign of
weakness if you take it easy sometimes
I need Shields I need Shields not a bird
something's not right not feeling so
good
oh
give me a warm fire and the book on
thermodynamic alloys I'd lead the way
but I do have the shortest legs head to
the objective everyone keep moving it
isn't far if we get there soon we might
have time for a snack hey if you make it
to the Waypoint I've got a juice box
with your name on it payload moving
payloads chugging along
payloads full steam ahead that's it for
the objective let's put a stop to that
the enemy is moving their barricade
that's not good we have to stop them
looks like it's up to me I always knew
it had come down to me whole fun and
Canes until someone gets hurt but a
riveting experience Tor burns on top
stay out of my systems all that
sophistication can't save you if you
can't stand the Heat
stay out of my way back to the slag
heaps they'll never hear the end of this
from Ingrid go on get out of here it's
an honor to get dismantled by me I told
you the size of the harm is not
important should have gotten the lead
home upgrade I planned that perfectly ha
and I only needed one eye don't tell
your mother about this all according to
design
scrapped I think you need more genetic
enhancements I think I've made
improvements to your face I always knew
your foolishness would be the end of you
don't underestimate a lint home he
walked right into that one
must be a bug in your system
slagged that's your last haunt that's it
back to the midden Heap this old screw
still got it you're not cut out for the
big leagues yet no didn't account for
that weak spot did you just doing my job
someone around here has to keep an eye
out you looked like you needed a hand
some Swedish Hospitality
you young chickens still have lots to
learn all hands to the objective hold
down the fort push them back they're
hurting my turret my baby's under attack
my turret's getting hit protect my
turret
my turret is being attacked my turret's
Under Fire
my turrets being destroyed enemy
teleporter located
foreign
[Applause]
hey keep working until the end
stand your ground until the end just a
little longer keep up our defense hold
your defenses for a little longer time's
running out put your backs into it
almost there keep pushing them back for
the alliance this will come in handy
they can always use more I can use this
oh yes come to me
no Trooper spot it no Troopers attacking
stop the payload people always
underestimate the engineers ah
[Music]
they can't drop my bomb in all the air
defenses are in place it'll work
so taking them out he's our top priority
Ironclad go get him the impressive
engineering takes after her old Papa
proud of you Bastion guess Brawn
sometimes does the trick
that gets my stamp of approval that gets
my seal of approval
they grow up so fast not the most
elegant but can't complain nice one they
teach you that in medical school great
can you do it again
that's my daughter they have a
teleporter find it
you should try my meatballs hurry over
here
stop lollygagging and get over here come
on spark plug that's done over here make
like a moose and run to my location add
up to an impressive top speed of 55
kilometers per hour come to the
objective he'll help get over here
poor Craftsman blames their tools
they're breaking through the doors are
giving out over there let's get the
objective moving to the destination
tracer's down we've got an ally town
they have a shield generator
too soon
gotcha I hear you clear as quartz loud
and clear understood of course let's get
to work moving the barricade time to
push
hammer down
oh that speed seems nice until you run
into a hammer hammered away
sorry thought you were a nail nailed it
that settles it every problem is a nail
knock knock
kapow
the most useful tool of them all
smack who needs a feast when you have a
hammer that's an Eradicator up ahead
watch out for the big Shield just what
the world needed they pushed past us
they have to take back the lead he lost
the lead Detonator coming from the right
Detonator incoming keep it away
Detonator coming from the left Detonator
coming right for us Detonator coming
behind us they need a Healer Detonator
destroyed
Show Yourself
enemy detected
someone's lurking over here come out
where I can see you
it's not quitting time yet I don't have
much time attack time's Running Out full
steam ahead no time fight all the way
into the tile time's running out put
your backs into it get to work time's
running out I need to attack over going
to lose hurry up and attack
fear like a cat walking around hot
porridge
attack
right on
Ironclad who are you before you enter
the monastery hi pardon the clean off
you're better than me in a fight I grant
you that but I still have the edge on
you in smithing touchy subject are you a
magic Spirit have you seen as much as I
have he either you laugh or you go mad
it is hard to trust that which I cannot
see with my own eyes never slain but I
will or I will die in the attempt I
fought it once or twice and have been
lucky only to lose what I have I was one
of many apprentices
but Rose the highest I'm still quite
handsome I'm beginning to think I should
have stayed on my boat I find your
religion unnerving monk they haven't
failed me yet I don't get it the dragon
though where exactly did you see it
Tavern brawl I hear you're an authority
on dragons
anyone I might know keep that weapon
loaded Outlaw they're only getting
started I hunt them we'll see if this
lord of the castle makes good on his
promises of payments
he seems like an untrustworthy sort not
tonight a dragon where because I could
not protect my Village against a dragon
attack I must atone for my failure
survive the night and I'll do so gladly
ah
be careful heads up what's here duh I
dropped it it just fell through my
fingers
oh
yeah
get our flag back recover our flag
[Laughter]
a man who felt a shadow attack attack
with me oh do I have to do everything
attack
hello there let's move the robot is in
my possession taking the robot how
riveting
oh
power overwhelming Fire King the bellows
time to let off some steam
maximum power
ing up the heat
I'm overloading
don't get caught with your beard in the
letterbox
snipers over there
she's over there time's running out put
your backs into it get to work time's
running out enemy Bastion scrapped I'm
ready to unleash the molten core My
ultimate is ready let's take their flag
attack the enemy's flag I've still got
the fire one eye one arm countless wings
who's next
I'm in the zone
short but deadly and that's how it's
done don't count the oldies out yet
everything is awesome it's not luck it's
all skill sometimes I surprise myself
um jump Jets concussion Rockets
well yes it's looking pretty good
I don't think they're compatible
slicer's incoming shoe they have our
flag get our flag back not your back
this is it protect the robot last chance
get that robot we can still win if we
take the robot that was a close call
Safe by a whisker someone revive Mercy
or it's going to hurt for the rest of us
someone Revive Our Ally Reinhardt needs
to be revived there's no prize for
coming in second nail them all let's
move this robot push the robot enemies
on the left enemies coming right at us
what's the right side they're attacking
From Below they're attacking from the
front enemies on the right the enemies
behind us they're below us they're
attacking from behind they're attacking
from above enemies above us watch the
left side guys all right through you
told of Amari to use my own Tech against
me you maniac that were you doing up
there couldn't we have talked this over
Reyes popped in the mouth right there in
the sky try to do that right in my face
you deserve what you got
looks like a fault in your jump pack
Winston don't play around with lava oh
sniped
they never expect a flying lint home
someone grab our flag they've dropped
our flag
heradicator spotted now this is what
proper engineering does for a city oh
these skyscrapers just hurt my neck New
York's Chief engineering advisor has
returned move out let's get down to
business broken safety compliances
everywhere
City of Lights I prefer the Northern
Lights time to show them who's boss
let's get her done
they need to fix that assassin
permanently take her out already
assassins down no more assassin tires
headed straight for us shock Tire Dead
Ahead it's coming across the bridge
huh
hard work pays off well the View's not
bad I've destroyed the shield Vale enemy
seal generator strapped just a few more
to go don't let up now
focus on the or-14s if we take them down
the rest should go easy
defend the objective get them off the
point move the payload guess I'm on
cleanup Duty returning the flag ah not
the eye get her off get off me
enemy teleports are destroyed piece of
junk join me
form up let's assemble our might group
up here group up with me group up group
up with me no
down
thanks thank you thank you much
appreciated thanks just a little longer
keep up our defense
you keep working until the end
not enough scrap
I'm out of scrap need more scrap got the
enforcer
enforcers down I agree
they need to clear the area there's an
assassin hear me baby hold together not
a chance I need armor
but I need armor or 14 engaging now
that's more like it time to get my hands
dirty
yes good good
they just need some time to get ready it
just needs some time to get warmed up
give it a second I built it of course
it's going to work no one asked for your
opinion it's just powering up I'll get
back to you on that
expert craftsmanship ready to activate
my molten core let's do this
let's hear those guns my masterpiece now
we're getting somewhere oh all right now
do what you were built to do ha no
that's what I had in mind go Tools in
hand praying in gear
[Laughter]
yeah
lots of Boston setting up take it out or
that gun will chew us to Pieces
Reinhardt your barrier would be a big
help now
destroy the teleporter find their
teleporter on my way there we go see
like I said it just needed a moment to
get warmed up not quite yet that hacks
going nowhere if someone doesn't stay on
it
one target left let's burn it down move
push forward I still have a few tricks
up my sleeve payloads ready to move I
told you it would work I'm on fire no
one can withstand me I'm a well-oiled
high power machine I'm at maximum
strength I'm hotter than a furnace novel
is getting the better of me
ah everyone get in here I'm not sure how
much those doors can take get them off
the doors hammered creasing the old
shoulder here's some percussive
maintenance hit the nail on the head
kapow My ultimate is still charging it's
too soon my ultimate is charging destroy
the objective an eventful wedding
after we Prevail will you join us for a
banquet Countess watch it anyone who
would willingly embrace the dragon's
fire is an Abomination I was thirsty so
I traded it to an old man for a drink
from Israel mind your defense the battle
is far from over you know what you're
all right Renegade is that even possible
I can handle myself mind your own battle
now I might be able to make a few
improvements to that weapon of yours
Outlaw the single-mindedness of Dr
junkenstein's Creations reminds me of
your own here are those who would give
their souls to serve those beasts my
people tend to some crazy nights you
weren't there monk you don't know about
my failure assassins over there
she's over there
the objective is damaged keep it up
[Music]
laughs
come on do I have to do everything
myself
they're dropping like flies looks like
it's up to me
this is why I prefer machines no why
didn't I think of that yes get to the
objective goodbye